

Muhammad Zaki **Ardianto**

Palmerah, West Jakarta City, Jakarta, Indonesia

Experienced and dedicated General Affairs with in-depth knowledge of managing an office, business development, administrative processes, managing successful relationships with employees. Ability to manage an organized database of company assets and employees by collecting records, and carefully organizing documents related to existing and future company business. Possess a positive attitude and strong work ethic.





(S) +62 812-1167-6405 M muhammadzakiardianto@gmail.com

Work Experience

Staff Operational • PT MBM

April 2022 - December 2022



- 1. Controlling every entry and exit of vehicle assets and company securities to tenant companies and PNM branches in Indonesia.
- 2. Made a breakthrough by installing a Barcode on every vehicle unit leased throughout Indonesia so that its usage track record can be tracked through the application.
- 3. Assisted in negotiating the disbursement of funds to the bank by mortgaging the company's securities assets in the form of thousands of motor vehicle letters to be able to pay off the company's trade payables.

Risk Management Section • PT MBM

PNM

March 2022 - April 2022

Assist the risk management department in controlling company assets in all branches in Indonesia in order to minimize the risks that occur that attack the company.

Procurement • PT MBM

PNM

January 2022 - March 2022

- 1. Procurement collects data, re-controls and conducts auctions and sales transactions for fixed buyers of PNM office motor vehicle asset units in all branches and external companies whose vehicle period has expired.
- 2. Receive new assets purchased by PNM.

Business Support • PT MBM

PNM

November 2021 - January 2022

- 1. Collect & create tax notices on company asset units in branches throughout Indonesia that are used by other external companies.
- 2. Re-control branch addresses as well as new branches and assets.
- 3. Create lease agreements & memorandums related to the company's business.

Marketing • PT MBM



October 2021 - November 2021

- 1. Confirmation of vendor cooperation for the sale of company vehicles and auctions by companies or individuals.
- 2. Customer service to branches and external companies with renewing rental agreements, auctioning vehicle units, routine service of rental vehicles as well as tax notices and unexpected financing complications of vehicle services
- 3. Coordinating with external companies as vendors for procurement of new vehicle units for procurement to branches

Education

2016 - 2022

Senior High School 44 Jakarta (Science)

Trisakti University

Department of Geological Engineering

Self-Ability

- Operating Microsoft Office well
- Able to solve problems at work
- Able to do Administration
- Able to work in teams and individuals
- Input data quickly and precisely
- Flexible and disciplined person
- Able to communicate and negotiate well
- Able to position themselves in the desired jobdesc

Language

- Indonesia
- English